

### **CONTACT INFO**

- 555729555
- Tbilisi, Tskneti, cholokashvili str. N88

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor degree**

georgian technical university

geology faculty

55 public school

## PERSONAL QUALITIES

- sociable
- Purposeful
- Confidence
- Detail oriented
- Critical thinking ability

# ACHI MAMUKASHVILI

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a motivated and customer-oriented individual with a strong passion for providing excellent service. I have valuable experience in maintaining positive client relationships, problem-solving, and ensuring a high level of customer satisfaction. I am adaptable, quick to learn, and excited to contribute to the welcoming atmosphere at working place. Additionally, I possess basic knowledge of web development, which has enhanced my time management and problem-solving skills.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### majorel

customer support

2021 - 2022

#### osint for ukraine

frotend developer

2022 - 2023

#### **EPAM** systems

javascript developer

2023-2024

#### **LANGUAGES**

Georigan (mother tongue)

**English**